Hi everyone! In today's video I'm going to explain how the credit statement
works and how to work out what you've made on any given day.
So first of all I've logged into my profile.
I'm now going to go to my details, credits, and click here on credit statement.
Here is your credit statement. This shows all of the transactions and all of
the credits that you've made since the very start of your webcam journey.
So here this last page is the most recent transactions and most recent credits
that you've made.
So what we're going to do is today I'm going to show you exactly how to work
out what you've made on any given day.
I'm going to choose the 5th of August. So to work out what you've made on any
given day you need to subtract what you started on that day from what you ended
on.
So let's start on what we ended on. So if we want to work out what we made on
the 5th of August we will go to the very last transaction on the 5th which is
here.
And we're going to go along and see what it was and what we ended on.
Okay so as you can see here we ended the 5th on 228.24 credits. So we're going
to put that into our calculator.
Okay I've now put that into my calculator. Now I'm going to see what I started
that day on.
So as you can still see here there's still transactions from the 5th here so we
need to go back at page to see if there are any more.
So we just click this arrow to go back one page.
So we need to find the 5th of the 8th here. We'll go down we should be able to
find it.
Okay there we go. There are a couple of transactions here on the 5th of the 8th
.
So we just need the very first transaction that's all we need to worry about
and we just need to see what the balance was at the very start of the day.
So as we can see the balance is 8.55 credits. So now we need to subtract that
from the final balance.
So I have a calculator what we ended that day on and now I'm going to subtract
8.55 from that. So I have 228.24 take away 8.55.
And that equals 219.69 credits. So that's how many credits we made on the 5th.
And we're not finished yet because this is how many credits you made to now
work how much that is in pounds, how much money you should expect in your bank
the next day.
We now need to take away 43.5%. So I'm going to do that on my calculator now.
So that leaves us with 124.12 pounds. So that's how much you should have in
your bank the next day.
So yes it's very simple to work out you just work out what you ended the day on
, subtract what you started the day on and then whatever that remaining balances
take away 43.5% and that's how much pounds you've made that day.
I'm now going to explain a couple more things on the credit statement.
So as you can see here the balance goes down to zero and again here and it says
it's a group transfer.
This basically is our payroll company transferring all of the credits out the
account.
This happens every week or so so don't worry about it.
It may happen when you're online it may happen halfway through the week.
It really doesn't matter and it's not something that you need to worry about.
The payroll company just have to transfer your credits out as obviously they
need to take the money out of the profile to then pay you.
Here as well it says available for transfer now.
You don't need to worry about this either. You do not need to transfer your
credits or payroll company to do everything for you.
They work out how much you've made, when to pay you, how to pay you and
everything that comes in between.
So you don't need to worry about this at all. You don't actually need to check
or worry about your credits at all because our payroll company, like I said, do
everything for you and pay you daily.
But if you do want to check what you've made each day you can just follow the
steps that I said earlier.
One final thing to remember with your credits.
We pay you daily like I said but if you don't hit 65 credits you won't get paid
the next day.
They will just sit in your balance here until you push it over 65 and then you
'll then get paid the next day.
And the day ends at 12 o'clock midnight so bear that in mind when working out
how much you've made.
I hope all that makes sense and if you have any more questions please ask your
mentor.